hey everyone welcome back to another
video on this channel today we are at
meritage homes on the far northwest side
of san antonio and as you can see
beautiful home built out of stucco
and stone and you have great north side
schools beautiful amenity center and
just a great fast and upcoming community
over here and today we are going to be
looking at a meritage home two-story
home
and just wait till y'all check this one
out so as soon as you come in you're
gonna have lvp
luxury vinyl plank
and let's just check this out
high ceilings
as soon as you come in you're gonna have
a flex room also known as an office
space and you have the ability to put in
closed doors right here this can be an
additional bedroom an office space a
game room a library
however
you please to use this room right here
so let's go ahead and check out
the other parts of this beautiful home
so as we continue down the foyer
to your right
you're gonna have your first half
bathroom
okay your first half bathroom
with a closet space right here and let's
check out the her score so the her score
is 59
and what this means is that the less the
score is the better
uh efficiency you have on your home
so this is amazing
um the foam insulation that they use
pretty much makes this home like a yeti
cooler can y'all believe that
and right here you're gonna have the
two-car garage
that you can't really see in here
really big garage
and it has we head over here you're
gonna have an open floor plan
okay so you're gonna have the kitchen
let's take a quick view and look of the
open floor plan
black cabinets with granite countertops
gas stoves
everything is beautiful in this home
especially for the price point
you have an on-site elementary school
on-site middle school and the high
school that you're going to be going to
is sotomayor hasn't even opened yet
opened in 2022 to 2023
school years so
check this out get your double sinks
dishwasher
for your backyard you're gonna have a
covered patio
so check this out this is beautiful
you cannot go wrong with san antonio a
home like this in california is
easily
a minimum of a million dollars
so you're going to have you know some
extra space right here which is really
unique
you know
this can be um a study room maybe even a
wine cellar
just i don't know but this is unique
just check out this extra closet space
right here
so this is unique as well
i love how they're maximizing all the
square footage in the home
so meritage homes is known for their
energy efficiency so you don't have to
be blowing that ac that heater all day
just the foam insulation that they use
is like a yeti cooler
so
blow the ac one time
you can leave it off for the next six
hours your home is gonna stay the same
so you're gonna save more money
on your utility bill every month
you're going to have high ceilings
let's go ahead and go upstairs
carpet with wood rattling
and wow this is really beautiful so
you're gonna have
a staircase that goes that way in that
way
and as we come to the right
you're gonna have the very first bedroom
okay this is cool i haven't seen a home
design like that ever that is awesome
so the older teenager gets all this room
all this space to themselves
walk-in closet with the option to turn
those wire shelves into wood shelves
let's take one more look
and if you're new to the channel make
sure you like and subscribe we post
everything san antonio related on this
channel to help people just like you
successfully relocate to san antonio and
see the variety of options san antonio
has to
offer so over here you're gonna have a
full bath
black cabinets
with white countertops
you're gonna have the great backsplash
tile
flooring as well
and welcome to your huge loft right here
also known as a second living room
with another bedroom right here so let's
check this out and then we'll go ahead
and check out the loft
beautiful spacious room as well um you'd
be surprised with the size of these
rooms in san antonio
right here is a good sized spacious room
nice huge loft
let's check out another angle
of this home
and location is everything when it comes
to buying a home so
i would rate this a an a
as far as location
a solid a not an a plus but a solid a
you have everything that you need in
this area
i'm assuming that's the master bedroom
we'll check that out last
you have your utility room upstairs
so washer dryer you don't have to go
down
and up
to wash clothes dry clothes
and you're gonna have
your last secondary bedroom
upstairs
before we head into the master bedroom
so check this out
and closets are pretty much all the same
we'll check out the closets really quick
boom
and you can definitely go ahead and give
me a text email call my team and i were
helping several families per month
successfully relocate to san antonio if
you have any questions you can
definitely give us a call i'll leave all
of my contact information
at the end of this video but it's also
in the description below as well
so
spacious
master bedroom
so as we head into the master shower
let's go ahead and check this out so
you're going to have double vanity sinks
right here
white countertops black cabinets
stand up shower
with a gray towel backsplash
and you're gonna go ahead and have a
peekable window right here with an
option to fog that out right there
um i've seen people even tense it where
they can see out but no one can see in
some extra closet space as well for your
towels soaps toiletries etc
you're gonna have your toilet right here
walk-in
ginormous closet
and if you are looking to relocate like
i said definitely give my team and i a
call email text we'd be more than happy
to serve and assist you any questions
you may have about san antonio as far as
affordability where to live etc we're
gonna be posting more content on this
channel so go ahead and give us a
subscribe a like and i'll see you on the
next video