welcome to my house tour
before we go into the house let's quickly look at the entry
from outside and now
we
go through the outer entry
and
enter
the
entrance hall
now here on the left
is a small
bathroom it is tiled
there is a
great
toilet
and
that's basically all of this tiled bathroom
then let's quickly go back into the entrance
and i'll just quickly close the door
yeah
now let's continue
on the right
is the kitchen as you can see we have a black marble countertops
and here is a small table
with a few utensils like the coffee machine
and an oven
to stay another glance
look at the beautiful black kitchen with the wooden countertops
i mean with wooden drawers
and that's basically it
then
we entered the living room
here we have
a
big table to etat
with nice black leather chairs
there is also a TV
right here
and then if we turn to the left we can see these so far slash couch section
with
a nice oven
as well as an aquarium
now let's quickly go outside
we also have this space here
with
another
sofa arrangement
this time it is outside though with a nice little
big plant here
and then another smaller TV
some nice audio equipment
and
then we go back inside
and again you can see the oven here
one last look at the table
and now we're going to take the stairs
to
get
to the
upper floor
which is the first floor
let's quickly take the stairs
you can see some plants here
and now we're on the first floor
here we have
another bathroom with
a nice
bathtub in the corner as well as another toilet
and a rock on the floor
and i now turn to the left
we enter
a
room
it has a
bird
as well as a
small TV
i can see
very simple
um
again here is a drawer and now we go back outside
and then he
here we have
a
small little office space
you can see a monitor on the office table we have a little bed as well
as a chair
and another
bigger
drawer
now we go back outside we go into another bedroom
again with a nice big bed
a nice black chair for clothes
and
uh
a nice
big
closet for clothes
as well
we now continue once more up the stairs
to the
topmost floor
in some flowers in the corner
and now we're on the top floor
here we have a room
with a bed on the side
as well as a nice comfortable
chair actually
two chairs and a little table
then there is another bed in the corner
and then
we can see another very big closet
and now if we peek around this corner
we can see another office desk as well as a gaming chair
and on top of the desk or two
laptops as well as a plant
and
that's
basically