hello everyone
today
we are going to
tour the student project house
o f
f e t h
zurich
and
you are going to create a three d mount model out of it
so
lets start walking towards
the building
so
that is a trash can
and a staircase
we are going up the staircase
that is
name played saying
it's the student project house
and this is the student project house door
that is
an led sign
and
welcome desk
screen
that is a lamp
and
a chair
lounger actually
and
some bursts
sure
statue's
and books
and pamphlets
what is the bicycle
thirty is another poster
and then
that seems like
an experiment
for some project
these are different project
prototypes
here
with a lot of stationery
do you have a lot of stationary here and chairs
and we have some
we have to notice board with a lot of posters and stickers
this is another project prototype
with the tree
and
another project prototype
and these are
this is the computer
another computer
a lot of three d printing machines
for making prototypes
more three d printing machines
then you will ever see
another computer
with the keyboard
and a c p u
my heater
chair
smart board
smart screen
these are
the
work desks
i don't know what the exactly called
something where
you can build
prototypes on
some cupboards
assink
and
toilet paper
with the trash can
a vacuum cleaner
another working station here
laminating machine
and i don't know what this is
we have some
baskets
and
the screen
some folders
share
another touch screen
a lot of stationary
and
the screen
some prototypes
jackets
for a lot of jackets
then we will start going up
this is another staircase and we are going to the floor e e
from here
and we see some chairs
and some
trash cans
hand the fridge
with beer cans and water bottles
v c
working
a set of working disks
a lot of chairs
the sofa
alam p
a whiteboard
marker pen
we see a few plants here
when some posters and some chairs
and we see a wash basin
with lot of dishes and
bottles
and
hand wash and dish wash
soak
up brush
some
tea
sashes is sugar
coffee machine
shops
paper cups classes
classics
and then we have a lot of baskets
and a lot of bottles